videos okay y'all want you want to tell the story or me you can tell it all right on christmas of
last year i was in a uh lapine lapine one of those and i saw a sister on the side just looked
like she was in just in distress in distress and i was waiting for my homegirl and i kept seeing
the sister over to the side and i was like it's christmas and she is in distress and when we
were leaving i asked you how you were doing what if you were okay yeah and you were like i'm trying
to get out of of new york and there was a situation going on yes and i was like well you really trying
to leave let me get you a ticket to atlanta and i got you the ticket to atlanta and she really left
because my face was covered your face was covered you just have a mask yeah i was covered up like
this hot in my face so this is your first time actually that's why when you came up there like
she doesn't recognize you i'm like i i couldn't right i'm so proud of you thank you and i'm so
glad i could be a part of your journey to helping yourself absolutely and thank you for receiving
my assistance yes come on oh my goodness yes thank you so much you're welcome keep going
i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry